Welcome back to the Dive Into Mark show!
We got a Roomba,
the dog is in hiding,
the kids are asleep,
and I finally shaved.
Mmmm... smooth.
In local news, the police installed
a speed trap right outside my house,
just in time for July 4th weekend.
Hey, thanks!
Unfortunately for them,
the tens digit is broken,
so it shows
"Your speed: 0, 1, 2, 3, 4..."
I feel safer already.
Last week, Cory Doctorow of
BoingBoing.net
announced that he was also
switching to Ubuntu
after 22 years of servitude to Apple.
I think I see the pattern.
Cory Doctorow is such a hard-core
Mac user that he actually has
a Sad Mac icon tattooed on his bicep.
And I thought I had migration problems.
In response to last week's show,
Dan Ridley writes,
"Okay, I feel totally gypped.
I downloaded your video, watched it,
and at no point during the video
did I actually see bunnies."
Did I mention we got a Roomba?
It's totally awesome.
It was actually a birthday present
for my wife.
Don't look at me in that tone of voice.
It's what she asked for.
I tried to talk her out of it.
We're still trying to decide
what to name it,
but my wife has announced
that it is definitely a boy.
She says she knows it's a boy because
of the way it waggles its butt
when it goes back to its home base.
I went to BJ's this weekend to buy
a ridiculous amount of
everything
and I parked next to a car that had a
bumper sticker that read,
"Sorry I missed church,
I was busy practicing witchcraft
and becoming a lesbian."
Apparently, this has been a popular
bumper sticker for some time,
but living in North Carolina,
this is the first I've seen of it.